本字幕由 YYeTs人人影视 原创翻译制作
仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
更多影视更新 请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
■
翻译：Soomii    红豆包    Iz    Ｊ小糯
校对：Ｊ小糯      时间轴：grace
■
后期：鱼骨头      总监：stephanie
《开心汉堡店》
第一季第五集
我要去参加告别单身女派对喽  好棒哦
That is the Bachelorette party! All right!
新娘结婚前邀请闺蜜参加的聚会
以庆祝新娘告别单身
要去脱衣舞会喽  美死了
Going to the strip club. All right.
要去吃泡菜喽
Going to pickles.
老公  我今晚要不要准备一些硬币呢
Boy, am I gonna need some quarters tonight. Ha ha!
-硬币  -对啊
- Quarters? - Yeah.
琳  你要硬币做什么
What are you gonna do with quarters, lin?
扔进脱衣舞女郎的丁字裤里
I'll plop them in their g-strings.
你要把硬币扔进她们的丁字裤里
You'll plop quarters in their g-strings.
-币无虚发  -叮叮当当咚
- Plop them right in. - Flippity flop.
-在泡菜俱乐部  -泡菜俱乐部
- At pickles. - Pickles.
为什么要叫"泡菜"呢
Why do they call it pickles?
因为他们供应泡菜
They actually serve pickles. Hmm.
我没开玩笑  他们的泡菜很好吃哦
No. I'm not kidding. They really have good pickles.
你以为它们不会好吃  其实真的很美味
You think they wouldn't, but they're delicious.
你要去晚宴剧场吗[餐后有戏剧表演的餐厅]
You're going to dinner theater, aren't you?
什么  你在说什么啊
Ha ha ha! What? What do you mean?
怎么可能  太疯狂了
Why, that's crazy.
好吧  鲍勃  被你猜着了
Fine, Bob. You got me.
我知道你肯定不准我去  所以扯了个慌
I know you don't approve of dinner theater, so I fibbed.
你知道吗  我宁愿你去脱衣舞会
You know what? I'd rather you go to a strip club.
老爸  晚宴剧场有什么不好的
What do you have against dinner theater, dad?
第一  吉恩  它既不是餐厅也不是剧场
Well, first of all, Gene, it's neither dinner nor theater.
这个剧场就像个人造奶酪
It's like the imitation cheese of theater.
听着不错  人造奶酪很好吃啊
Sounds fun. Imitation cheese is delicious.
真是我的乖儿子  一闪一闪亮晶晶
That's my boy. That's my star.
琳达  你知道真正的问题出在哪么
Linda, you know what the real problem is?
出在哪
What?
是晚宴剧场给你带来的后遗症
It's the result of dinner theater,
它让你无时无刻不在唱歌
what it does to you, makes you sing everything.
谁打的
Who was that?
打错了
Wrong number.
早餐吃什么
So what's for breakfast?
鸡蛋  鸡蛋  鸡蛋
Eggs, eggs, eggs.
鸡蛋  鸡蛋  鸡蛋  鸡蛋
Eggs, eggs, eggs, eggs.
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
我说  琳  来动动嘛
So, Lin, hey, it's uh... all right.
-今晚不行  不行  -好吧
- Not tonight, no. - Okay.
今晚不行  不行
Not tonight, no.
我知道了
I get it.
之后的一整个礼拜你都会这样  是吧
And so you're gonna be doing that all week, right?
不
No...
是的
Yeah!
斜坡上的百老汇
《风流倜傥大海盗》  正在上演
我们喝酒  抢劫  强奸  扫射
We drink, we loot, we rape, we shoot
我们唱歌  跳舞  旋转  腾跃
We sing, we dance, we twirl, we prance
我们是风流倜傥的大海盗
We're the pirates of panache
琳达  快和我说说
Linda, tell me everything.
莫特  我跟你说
Oh, Mort, I'm telling you,
如果可以从头再活一次
to be in dinner theater...
我想在晚宴剧场度过
if I could do my life over again,
如果能有这么一个机会该有多好
oh, if I could,oh... I could just have one chance...
-你会那样做吗  -是啊
- You'd do that? - Yeah.
琳达  你在说什么呢
Linda, what are you talking about?
你的人生已经很美好了  你在餐馆工作
You've got a great life. You work in a restaurant.
你要为全世界供应汉堡  是吧
You get to feed the world, right?
没错
Right.
上礼拜有个加拿大人来我们店
There was someone in here from Canada last week,
还记得吗
remember?
我们还了解了很多加拿大的国情
And we learned all about that country.
是不错
It's great.
我讨厌那个国家
I hate that country.
琳达  你已经拥有一家餐馆
You know, Linda, you've got the dinner part already.
你懂我意思
You know what that means.
你就要举办一场...
You're halfway to doing...
接着说
Yeah?
属于你自己的...
your own...
快说  快说  什么  什么
Say it. Yeah. Say it. What? What?
晚宴剧场
Dinner theater.
属于你自己的晚宴剧场
Your very own dinner theater.
晚宴剧场  好耶好耶
Dinner theater. Yes! Yeah!
我们高兴个啥劲啊
Yay! Why are we excited?
汉堡晚宴剧场
Hamburger dinner theater?
别这样  鲍鲍
Oh, come on, Bobby?
我们每天都努力干活
We work hard everyday
让你的梦想成真
to make your dream come true.
为什么不让我的梦想也成真一下下呢
Why can't we do my dream, too?
你的梦想要持续多长时间呢
About how long do you think your dream will take,
一个小时吗  还是一个半小时
like an hour, hour and a half?
你疯了吗
You crazy?
至少签约三个星期
It's got to be at least a three-week engagement.
三个星期  三天怎么样
Three weeks? How about three days?
好吧  就这么定了
All right. We'll take it. Ha ha!
一定会很精彩的
This is gonna be wonderful.
那要演什么呢
What's the show gonna be?
谋杀  谋杀悬疑剧
Ah, murder. Murder mystery. Ach.
-连环谋杀悬疑剧怎么样  -好啊好啊
- How about mass murder mystery? - Okay. Sure.
-编成歌舞剧怎么样  -好啊
- And a musical? - Of course.
能不能再加上爱情元素
Can it also be a love story?
一出连环谋杀爱情悬疑歌舞剧的背景发生在
Aw, a mass murder mystery musical love story set in...
纳粹德国
Nazi Germany.
-在蒙特利尔  -我受够加拿大了
- Oh, in Montreal. - Enough with Canada!
在番茄酱加工厂
In a ketchup factory,
一个撩人的番茄酱加工厂怎么样
a sexy ketchup factory?
我想到了  在太平间
I got it! In a morgue!
我可以提供道具
I have props.
拉倒吧
Oh, come on.
对对  莫特  就这个了
Yes. Yes. Mort, that's it.
我们就叫它"梦想火葬场"
We'll call it "Dreamatorium".
真的吗
Really?
梦想火葬场
Dreamatorium,
发生在梦想火葬场
it's a dreamatorium.
看看这个布景  我是在太平间吗
Look at this set. Am I in a morgue?
真有身临其境的感觉
Oh, it feels like I am.
让我高兴的是
I am just so happy
我们大家都对晚宴剧场着了迷
we've all been bitten by the dinner theater bug.
吉恩  声响效果自然由你来负责
Now, Gene, you're on sound effects, naturally.
-吓人吧  -真恐怖
- Ominous. - Chills. Oh.
记住
Remember,
每个角色都有出场和退场音乐
every character gets some intro and outro music.
没问题
You got it.
别  别把我算进去
Don't. Don't score me.
莫特  你来负责视觉效果
Mort, you're on visual effects.
用人造血浆  还是来真的呢
Fake blood... Or is it?
现在  来说下剧本
Now, script.
大家都知道
As you know,
每个进入这间太平间的人都被神秘地杀害了
everyone who enters my morgue is mysteriously killed.
莫特  你演运尸工  被害人一号
Mort... body delivery guy, victim one;
吉恩  送花员  被害人二号
Gene... flower delivery guy, victim two;
蒂娜  大树  被害人三号
Tina... tree, victim three;
露易丝  你来当管家
Louise... the Butler
大家都认为你是杀人凶手
who everyone thinks is the killer.
你只是个烟幕弹
You're the red herring.
蒂娜是一棵树  被谋杀的树
Tina's a tree? That gets killed?
她想演大树  就可以演大树
She wants to be a tree, she can be a tree.
蒂娜会怯场
Tina has got stage fright.
我会怯场吗
I have stage fright?
是的  宝贝  你打小就怯场
Yeah, sweetie, ever since you were a little baby.
蒂娜  叫妈咪
Tina, say "Mommy".
妈咪
Mommy.
妈  不对
Ma. No.
我会一直剪  你说停我就停
I'll keep cutting. You say when.
这里是911  请问有什么紧急情况
911. What's your emergency?
蒂娜  快来帮忙
Tina! Help!
还在吗
Hello?
蒂娜  着火了
Tina! Fire!
还真是能说
That explains a lot.
鲍鲍  有一个小角色我希望由你来演
Now, Bobby, there's a small part I'd like you to play...
树医  他想拯救那颗大树
the tree surgeon who tries to save the tree
却变成了被害人四号
but instead becomes victim number four.
我很想演  但绝对不行
I'd love to, but absolutely not.
我已经负责晚宴剧场的餐饮部分  琳
I'm already doing the dinner part of this dinner theater, Lin,
我一个人打理  可能会忙不过来
by myself, I might add.
-就一句台词  -不行
- It's one line. - No.
怎么了嘛
What's the matter?
你怕会上瘾吗
Afraid you might get bitten?
-揭穿你啦　哈哈  -有意思
- Bzz bzz bzz! Gotcha! Ha ha! Yeah. Okay. - Good.
我们现在就来演一出  来嘛
Let's do a scene right now. Come on.
-我们来个即兴表演  -即兴表演
- Let's do an improv. - An improv?
对  即兴表演
Yeah, an improv.
我  你好  你叫什  你好呀
I... hi. What's your... Hi. How are you?
我只是在这里站着
I'm just standing out here.
我也是啊
So am I.
-外面可真冷  -还好吧
- It's cold out. - Not really.
我穿着一件大外套
I have a big coat on.
看  演得很不错嘛  很不错
See? You're good. You're good.
-演得真不错  -我不喜欢
- That was good. - I don't like it.
-我不喜欢  -真不错
- I don't like it. - Yes.
只是一段情景
That was a whole scene.
就演成了一出戏  我喜欢
It just becomes a play. I love that.
那出戏应该由我们来演
That's the play we should do.
我们就叫它"大外套"吧
We'll call it "Big coat."
梦想火葬场
晚宴剧场
红外套  黄外套
Red leather, yellow leather.
你是在和我说话吗
Um, are you taking to me?
我正在彩排  真难以置信
I'm warming up my instrument! Unbelievable!
对不...
I'm sor... uh...
对不起  演出前我会紧张
Hey, I'm sorry. It's preshow nerves.
过来  来抱抱  求好运
Come here. Hug for luck.
你这个变态的白痴
You freaking idiot!
剧场里不许拥抱求好运
You don't hug for luck in the theater!
别出声  别出声
Shh shh shh. Shh shh.
抱歉  宝贝  别出声
I'm sorry, baby. Shh shh.
我不是那个意思  宝贝
I didn't mean it, baby.
你知道我在演出前是什么样
You know how I get before a big show.
你知道我是什么样的
You know how I get.
别碰我  你把我的妆都弄花了
Get off of me! You're smudging my makeup!
你想让我带着这副脏兮兮的妆容
You want me to go out there in front of these people
站在那些人面前吗  你这蠢小子
with this makeup all smudged, you clumsy oaf!
抱歉  宝贝  快过来
Sorry, baby. Come here.
晚上好  女士们
Good evening, ladies.
请进　好好享受
Please enter and be tained.
我不明白  鲍勃
I don't get it, Bob.
为什么大家吃汉堡还要买票
Why are people buying tickets to your burger?
琳达正在编排一出戏
Linda is putting on a dinner theater,
所以你付的是演看戏和汉堡钱
so you're paying for the entertainment plus the burger.
如果有人只想吃汉堡呢
What if someone only wants to eat a hamburger?
那就只需付汉堡钱
I guess you could just pay for the burger
然后背对舞台就行了
and turn your back to the stage.
你知道的  我可以这样看戏
I could kind of watch like this, you know,
用我的余光
with my peripheral vision.
有个诚信制度  泰迪
It'd be the honor system, Teddy.
我是说  如果你发现自己在看演出
I mean, if you find yourself watching the show,
你就应该买票  对吗
you should probably buy a ticket, right?
那很公平  绝对公平
Oh, that's fair. That's more than fair.
别出声  泰迪  演出时你不能说话
Shh, but, Teddy, you can't talk during the show.
不不不  我明白
No, no, no. I get it.
-有一次我在剧院里看电影  -泰迪  别出声
- One time I was at the movies, right, - Teddy! Shh!
这家伙的电话吵个不停
and this guy's phone goes off during...
泰迪  要开始了
Teddy, they're starting.
这家伙的电话吵个不停
And this guy's phone goes off...
别讲故事了  泰迪
Don't tell the story, Teddy.
-他拿起电话  -别讲了  闭嘴
- And he picks up the phone... - Don't tell... shh!
看电影的人都在说"别打了"
And everyone in the theater is like, "Stop it"...
泰迪  停  别讲了
Teddy, stop. Stop telling...
大家都在议论谁是凶手
and everyone is like, "Who's the killer?"
-闭嘴  -好  不对
- Shut your mouth. - Right. No.
-那个家伙就是那么做的  -闭嘴
- That's what that guy did. - Shut your mouth.
万物消逝
Everything dies...
除却爱情
but love.
晚上好
Good evening.
这是个爱情故事  但会有凶杀情节
This is the story of love, but there will be a murderer,
由你们来猜谁是凶手
and it's up to you to guess who that murderer is.
小提示  不是我哦
Hint... it's not me...
我是葛莱蒂丝  一个寂寞的太平间业主
Because I'm just Gladys, a lonely morgue owner.
据说大多数人都是在工作中找到的真爱
You know, they say most people find love where they work.
看看我的工作环境
Well, look where I work.
寂寞的太平间业主  您的尸体到了
Corpse delivery for a lonely morgue owner.
我就是
That would be me.
有人把我杀死了
I've been murdered to death.
今晚并没有发生凶杀案
So no actual murder tonight,
只是一些人造血浆和器官
just a lot of fake blood and fake organs.
是啊  对  对  都是假的
Yeah. Right. Right. Fake.
是的  大概伤口边的血做得有点夸张了
Yeah. We might have overdone it a little on the gore.
无人死伤
Well, no harm done.
但是大家被吓得不轻
Except for the people being treated for shock.
是啊　他们都要求退款了
Yeah, and the people who demanded their money back.
下一场演出会更精彩
Well, the next performance is gonna be really great.
下一场演出
Next performance?
今晚的灾祸还不能让这场晚宴闹剧中止吗
Wasn't tonight's debacle the end of dinner theater?
我只要为明天的演出微调下道具就行了
I just need to tweak some stuff for tomorrow's show,
-也许减少点喷血量  -什么
- maybe tone down the blood a smidge. - What?
我一直在思考
I've been thinking.
我想克服怯场的毛病
I want to get over this stage fright.
我想来句台词
I think I'd like to have a line.
鲍勃  我们的小树长大发芽开始说话了
Aw, Bob, our tree is growing up and sprouting words.
我来编句你明晚表演的台词
Let's write you a speech for tomorrow night's performance.
我能说"不  不要"吗
Can I say, "No. Don't"?
那正是树会说出的话
That's exactly what a tree would say.
明晚之前我会背熟这句台词
I'll have it memorized by tomorrow night.
琳　你在舞台上实现了几分钟你的梦想
Lin, you lived out your dream on stage for a couple minutes,
既然演出不收费
and since there were no charges filed,
你就可以一直把梦做下去  对吗
they can never take that away from you, right?
鲍勃  我的梦想还没有实现呢
Bob, my dream has not been... satisfied.
-演出必须继续  老爸　-没错
- The show must go on, dad. - Yeah.
你做完第一个汉堡后放弃了吗
Did you give up after you made your first burger?
没到最后就不算结束
It ain't over till it's over.
没有  你还加了蒜粉
No. You added garlic powder.
幸运是百分之九十的准备
Luck is 90% preparation and...
吉恩  够了
Gene, enough.
好吧  再演两场戏
Oh, two more shows.
这玩意没有一点血的味道
This tastes nothing like real blood.
梦想火葬场
晚宴剧场
最后两场　血量减少20%
寂寞的太平间业主  您的鲜花到了
Flowers for a lonely morgue owner.
我就是
That's me.
天啊  我的肚子上好像插进一把利刃
Oh, God! That feels like a sharp knife in my belly.
喂  吉恩
Psst, Gene.
吉恩  吉恩
Gene. Gene.
干嘛
Yeah?
死完了吗
Are you done?
没呢
No.
你得去为三号桌送餐
I need you to serve this to table three.
鲍勃  别出声  他快死了
Bob, shh! He's dying.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
过来
Come on... ahem.
过来  管家  我们去公园
Come on, Butler. Let's go out into the garden.
蒂娜  蒂娜  到你说台词了
Tina. Tina, it's your big line.
-说啊  -不  不要
- Go. - No. Don't.
这棵树  它被杀死了
The tree, it's been murdered.
管家  是谁杀了他们呢
Oh, Butler, who is committing all these murders?
真是问住我了  我的刀在这儿呢
Beats me. Oh, there's my knife.
我当然不知道是谁干的啦
Well, I sure don't know whodunit.
你们知道吗
Do you?
杀人凶手是大树
Is the tree the murderer,
还是送花员
or is the flower delivery man the murderer,
或者是这个可疑的管家
or perhaps the suspicious Butler.
你们都错了
Well, you're all wrong.
杀人凶手就是我
The murderer was me. Ha ha!
搞什么  你明明在开场时说过
What? You explicitly told us at the beginning of the show
你不是杀人凶手
you weren't the murderer.
没错  可剧情转折了嘛
That's right. It's a twist.
不  你在撒谎  撒谎可不是剧情的转折
No. It's a lie. A lie is not a twist.
别紧张  你不是第一次干这个了
Don't be nervous. You do this all the time.
如果想要演员们的签名
The cast will be signing autographs
我们会满足大家的要求
if anyone would like one.
所有人坐回原位  马上
Everyone back in their seat! Now!
我是来打劫的
This is a robbery.
打劫  这才是转折嘛
A robbery. Now, that's a twist.
我们的表演没有这部分  各位
This is not part of the show, people.
这是真的打劫  孩子们  到柜台后面来
This is a real robbery. Kids, get behind the counter.
我们俩可以把这货拿下
We can take this guy.
我攻上面  你攻下面
I go high. You go low.
-等下  你说什么  -算了  算了
- Wait. What? - Never mind. Never mind.
-等等  -你搞砸了  都怪你  蒂娜
- Wait. - You blew it. You blew it, Tina.
每个人都给我待着别动
Everyone stay where you are.
-把收银机里的东西都给我  -好  好
- Give me everything in the register. - Yeah. Fine.
听着  这儿有孩子  所以别干蠢事
Listen. There are kids here, so don't do anything stupid -er
别干比抢劫更蠢的事
than rob this place.
-闭嘴  老油条  -别叫我老油条
- Shut up, greaseball. - Don't call me greaseball...
你还面具脸呢
Uh, mask face.
这不是在表演
It's not part of the show.
表演
Show?
吉恩  别弹了
Gene, stop.
放轻松  别激动
Just take it easy.
我会...  放轻松的
Oh, I'll take it...easy.
他们又加了一出打劫的戏
Hmm, they added a robbery element to the show.
-真聪明  -滑雪面罩做得有点土
- That's clever. - The ski mask is a little cheesy.
我觉得挺好看的嘛
I think it looks pretty good.
全都在这了
Okay. That's all of it.
你拿到钱了  可以走了吧
You've got your money. Now be on your way.
给我来点音乐
Give me a little music.
拜托  快走吧
Oh, come on. Just go.
最后  那句  台词  再来  一遍
Do your last line again.
说
Go.
你拿到钱了  可以走了吧
You've got your money. Now be on your way.
我或走  或留
Maybe I'll leave, and maybe I'll stay.
也许聚光灯
Maybe it's the limelight
会化作歌声
could be the singing.
该打911了
911 should be a-ringing.
我却停不下来
But I can't stop.
我与你一样
And neither can I.
坐下  都给我坐下
Sit down. Sit down!
开玩笑的  大家都站起来吧  站起来
I'm kidding. Everyone up. Come on.
这不是在表演
It's not part of the show.
快弹退场音乐
Play me out.
能破开五块钱吗  我想给演员们付点小费
Can you break a five? I'd love to tip out the cast.
不  我破不开  这位女士
No! I can't break a five, lady!
我刚才被抢了  你没看到吗
I was just robbed! Did you not just see that?
你就站在那儿  白痴
You were standing right here, idiot!
-你们可真敬业  -给我出去
- Oh, you people commit. - Get out!
没能阻止昨天的抢劫  我们深感遗憾
We feel terrible we didn't stop that robbery last night.
昨天的抢劫真是太可怕了
Oh, that robbery was horrible. Ohh!
但我不得不说  听到观众们为我们鼓掌
Though I have to admit, it felt so good
那感觉真是棒极了
to hear the audience applaud.
你们是在说昨天的表演吗
Are you guys talking about that show last night?
我觉得演的真让人目不暇接
I thought it was dazzling.
是吗  你来看"梦想火葬场"了吗
Oh, yeah? You saw Dreamatorium?
我只看了后面
Yeah. I caught the end of it.
我觉得演劫匪的人是全场的亮点
I thought the guy who played the robber really stole the show.
你们来这儿是为了他吗
Is that why you guys are here?
不  他们来这儿是因为那是个真的劫匪
No. They're here because the robber was a real robber
他劫走了我227块大洋
and he stole 227 bucks.
没那么多吧
A little less than that.
要抓住这个人会很难
It'll be hard to catch this guy.
没人看清他的脸
Nobody got a good look at him.
把这个写到你们的报告里
Put this down in your report.
他的气宇堪比男主角
He was leading-man handsome.
他带着滑雪面罩呢
He was wearing a ski mask.
他有伯特・雷诺兹年轻时的气度
Well, he had the presence of a young Burt Reynolds.
还有能和老戴比・雷诺兹媲美的鸡鸡
And the pipes of an old Debbie Reynolds.
网上评价出来了
Hey, the on-line reviews are in.
来听听这个
Listen to this one.
来自网友"谁是你爹1997"
It's from hoosierdaddy1997.
情节狗屁不通
"The plot made zero sense,
布景完全是小屁孩做出来的
and the set looked like children made it..."
没错  确实是孩子做出来的  我的孩子
Yeah. Children did make it... my children.
但"梦想火葬场"吸引人的地方
"But the reason to go see Dreamatorium
是它的结尾
is the closing musical number."
劫匪的和寂寞的太平间业主
"The chemistry between the robber character
两个角色间的化学反应可以说是火花四溅
and the lonely morgue operator was sparktastic."
有人提到食物吗
Did anyone mention the food?
没有
Uh... no.
非常好  也就是说抢劫的桥段广受好评
Great. So the robbery got rave reviews.
鲍勃  我们成功了
Bob, we're a hit.
不  琳达  我们被劫了
No, Linda. We were hit.
这段不错
Good one.
-对  很巧妙  -过奖了
- Yeah. That's good. - Hey, thanks.
-我没懂  -我们被劫了
- I don't get it. - We were hit.
"演出成功"也有"被劫"的意思  对吗
A hit is, am I wrong, is a robbery, right?
没错  "演出成功"也有"被劫"的意思
Right. A hit is a robbery.
严格说来  对于警察
Well, technically, for the cops...
严格说来我们不这么说
Technically, no.
算了  算了
Forget it. Forget it.
外行才这么说
But in layman's terms...
-别说了  各位  -没人被打啊
- Forget it, everybody. - Nobody got hit.
大家都别说了
Everybody forget it.
瓦格斯塔夫小学
我们  演绎着自己的人生
There we were, putting on the show of our lives,
当时一名男子持枪冲了进来
when in walked a man with a gun in his hand,
他在找那个神秘人
and he was looking for you-know-who.
你们现在可以提问了
We will now take questions.
选我  选我
Oh! Me. Oh! Oh!
大号汤米
Large Tommy.
我要问蒂娜  你当时害怕吗
Question for Tina. Were you scared?
不  她不怕
No. She wasn't.
中号珍妮
Normal-size Jenny.
枪有多大  有人中枪吗
How big was the gun, and did anyone get shot?
你问了两个问题了
That's a two-part question.
不予回答
I don't answer those.
小号彼得
Tiny Peter.
这是不是代表你们现在成立帮派了呢
Does this mean you're in a gang now?
没错
That is correct.
我们的帮派叫作"玻璃碴儿童"
Our gang is called "the Broken Glass Kids".
你们可得小心了
We'll cut you.
我已经等不及今晚的演出了
Ach, I can't wait for the show tonight.
什么  今晚
What, tonight?
我还以为你会考虑取消呢
I thought maybe you'd consider canceling,
看来不让我郁闷  你就不罢手
but you're really committed to making me unhappy.
没有劫匪  演出就变味了
The show won't be the same without the robber.
怎么  你们都在想这件事
What? You're all thinking it.
同意之至
I got to agree.
那家伙唱得好
That guy could really sing...
抢得妙
and rob.
我们再一次致以歉意
Well, again, our apologies.
我们一得到消息就会跟进这个案子
We'll follow us as soon as we hear anything.
仍然为你们感到高兴
So happy for you, though.
谢谢
Thanks. Ahh...
莫特  你说得对
Mort, you're right.
没有劫匪我可怎么办
What am I gonna do without the robber?
你只要...
You'll just have to...
沉住气  就好
take it easy
等一下  那个声音
Wait a minute. That voice.
我的天啊  是你
Oh, my God, it's you.
-你就是那个劫匪  -不敢当
- You're the robber. - Guilty.
昨夜意义非凡  是吧
Last night was something, wasn't it?
我知道  我们两个很来电
Oh, I know. We were electric together.
那我们今晚再来一次吧
So let's do it again tonight.
是的  我想举报一起...
Yes. I want to report a...
你这是干什么  琳达
What are you doing, Linda?
我要让警察逮捕这个强盗
I'm getting this guy arrested.
不要  他还想再演一次呢
No, but he wants to do the show again.
他持枪劫了我们
He robbed us with a gun.
各位  别激动
Hey, everyone relax.
那把枪不是真的  是假的
It wasn't even a real gun... fake,
此刻正在我的另一件夹克衫里
and currently in my other jacket
它们在我车子的后备箱锁着呢
locked in the trunk of my car.
鲍勃  他想来表演
Bob, he wants to perform.
这个人是我节目缺少的那份配料
This guy is the missing ingredient to my show.
他是我的蒜粉
He's my garlic powder.
没错  抢我餐馆的那个劫匪此刻就在这里
Yes. The man who robbed my restaurant is here right now.
身高约5英尺8英寸  体重有150磅吧
He's about 5'8", maybe 150 pounds.
我不太擅长估计体重  所以...
I'm bad at guessing weight, though, so...
我插一句
Yeah. I'll say. Yeah.
-160磅  -真抬举我
- 160? - Oh, flatterer.
好吧  170磅
All right. 170.
再打给你
Call you back.
-你刚才说枪在车里  -骗你的
- You said the gun was in your car. - I lied.
-你还说枪是假的  -也是骗你的
- What about it being fake? - Also a lie.
看见了吧  撒谎可以成为剧情的转折
See? A lie can be a twist.
既然你报了警  我就要抢钱
Since you did that, I'm gonna do this.
-打开收银机  -好极了  又被抢了
- Register. - Great. Again.
祝没有我的今晚好运
Good luck tonight without me.
我们忘记把这个给你们了
We forgot to give this to you...
很抱歉让劫匪逃走  这块蛋糕聊表心意
a little "Sorry we let the robber get away" bundt cake.
你们又让他逃走了
You're doing it again.
他刚刚与你们擦肩而过
He just ran right past you.
鲍勃  等一下
Hold that thought, Bob.
抢劫我们的劫匪刚刚又抢了我们一遍
The guy who robbed us just robbed us again.
等等  分队  你能重复一下吗
Hold on. Can you repeat that, dispatch?
他说的正是我在说的
He's saying what I'm saying.
那个劫匪  刚刚离开
The guy who robbed us, he just left.
我们得走了  鲍勃
We got to go, Bob.
那个抢你们的劫匪刚被在此区域出没
The guy who robbed you was just spotted in the area.
别抓他  别抓他  别抓他  别抓他
Don't catch him. Don't catch him. Don't catch him. Don't catch him.
他被抓住了
They got him.
老天  那个茱莉亚揍得可真狠
Jeez, that Julia packs a wallop.
你就是不让我的梦想实现  是吧
Ah, you couldn't just let me have my dream, could you?
什么  就因为我报了警
What? You mean, cause I called the police?
那个人犯下持械抢劫罪  琳  两次
The guy committed armed robbery, Lin, twice.
而你犯了谋杀罪  鲍勃
But you committed murder, Bob.
你一枪打爆了我的梦
You blew my dream's head off.
你也太戏剧化了  琳
That's a little dramatic, Lin.
没错  鲍勃  因为我以前是演员
Yes, Bob, because I used to be an actor.
"梦想火葬场"只剩两张票了哦
Only two tickets left for Dreamatorium,
多于三人的表演有更新哦
the show over three people have been blogging about.
各位  这是最后一场演出了
Final performance, people.
你今晚会说出台词吗
Do you think you're gonna say your line tonight?
大概不会吧
Probably not.
你知道吗  战胜怯场的一个好办法就是
You know, a good way to beat the stage fright...
想象观众们一丝不挂
imagine the audience naked.
我已经做过了  想象所有人都全身赤裸
I already do that. I imagine everyone naked.
所有人  同一时间
Everyone? All the time?
是啊  你不这样幻想吗
Yeah. You don't do that?
不
No.
那再试着想象他们都穿着衣服
Well, try picturing the audience with clothes on, then.
穿得严严实实的吗
Like all their clothes?
只戴套套和帽子就好
Well, maybe just a condom and a hat.
好
Okay.
今晚的票终于都卖光了  座无虚席呀
Tonight's show is officially sold out, packed house.
老妈  你激动吗
Are you feeling it, mom?
老爸  你激动吗
Whoo! Are you feeling it, dad?
谁在乎这事啊
Eh, who cares?
观众满心期望夺目的演出
The audience is expecting to be dazzled,
可是大明星不会来了  这多亏了你老爸
but thanks to your father, we have no star.
我们去演大家都讨厌的那个版本吧
Let's just go do the version everyone hated.
凶手是谁
Whodunnit?
是运尸工
Was the murderer the corpse delivery guy,
还是送花员
or was it the flower delivery guy,
或是这个贼眉鼠眼的管家
or was the murderer the shifty Butler?
都不是  凶手就是我
Wrong. The murderer was me.
谢谢大家  晚安
Thank you. Good night.
等一下  我看过昨晚的演出
Hold on. I saw the show last night.
相信我  重头戏没演呢
Trust me, it's about to get good.
大家  演出结束了哦
That's our show, everyone.
请离场
Thanks for coming out.
那个出彩的神秘演员呢
What about the you-know-who surprise performer?
好吧  我们的演出就是这个样子的
Yeah. Well, the show is what it is, so...
晚安
good night.
我来告诉你是什么样子的  就是堆垃圾
I'll tell you what it is. It's garbage.
好了好了  路上小心
Okay. All right, then. Drive safe.
不许动  我要打劫
Nobody move! This is a robbery!
我说了  坐回去  女士  我要开枪了
I said, sit back down, lady, or I'll shoot!
鲍鲍  你来演戏了
Aw, Bobby, you're in the show.
-垃圾  -我不想要你们的钱
- Garbage. - I don't want your money.
我只想要这家大款店主的钱
I just want the money of the big shot who owns this place.
亲爱的 这是一种犯罪方法呢
Ooh, way to commit, honey.
我的天  我觉得今天的演出要好多了
Boy, I thought we did better today.
好了  继续
All right. Here it goes.
我在边唱边填词
So I'm singing words to a song,
歌词是现编的
I'm making up right now.
因为重要的是歌词
Cause it's the singing that matters,
曲调无所谓
and not the song.
-现在由我...  -来...
- So it's up to me... - to...
唱...  个...
sing... in...
高调
key
-调  -调
- ey - ey
-感觉好棒  -没错  只是有点...
- That was great. - Yeah. Just go...
-怎么  -有点高
- What? - It's a little high.
-我承认  -你唱得有点高
- Well, I nailed it. - You were a little high.
那你就再高点
So you go higher.
大家都走了  我想我们可以停了
I think everyone is gone. Yeah. I think we can stop.
是我们把他们清出去的
We cleared them out.
不  不要
No. Don't.
我说出来了  蒂娜  快鞠躬谢场
I did it. Tina, take a bow, girl.